UBISOFT PRESENTS
Ubisoft 呈献
TOM CLANCY'S RAINBOW SIX SIEGE
DEV DIARY - ESPORTS YEAR 3
《彩虹六号：围攻》第三年度电竞赛事开发日志
TOM CLANCY'S RAINBOW SIX SIEGE
DEV DIARY - ESPORTS YEAR 3
《彩虹六号：围攻》第三年度电竞赛事开发日志
today I'm excited to be talking about
今天我非常激动地跟你们介绍
（电竞经理 Cary Lambert）
today I'm excited to be talking about
今天我非常激动地跟你们介绍
（电竞经理 Cary Lambert）
some of the upcoming changes to pro league starting next season
一些即将在下一个赛季实装在职业联赛中的变化
PRO LEAGUE FORMAT
职业联赛赛制
first up one of the major changes
第一个我们正在进行的改动
that we're making is we are extending the pro league to a six month period
就是我们打算将职业联赛延长为为期六个月
spread out over 14 play days
延长至超过十四天
where each team will play every other team twice
每一支队伍会与其他队伍进行两场角逐的赛程
matches will now be in a best-of one essentially
此后的比赛会变得更有效率
making each team's performance against their opponent a best of two
且确保队伍在一个良好的状态中进行，
并以最优秀的表现来与自己的两个对手竞争
simply put we're moving away from the old bracketed format
简言之 我们正在将旧的晋级赛制移除
and switching to this double round-robin approach
然后将其转变为这种双循环赛制
we hope this approach will be fair
我们希望这样的尝试是公平的
allowing teams more opportunities to prove their worth
允许队伍拥有更多的机会来证明他们自身的价值
this also meansthat each team will play every week
这同样意味着每支队伍每周都将会进行比赛
giving fans more opportunities to catch their favorite teams in action
给观众带来更欣赏他们所喜爱的队伍比赛的机会
now of course having a six month season
如今 毫无疑问的是进行长达六个月的赛程
does mean that there will be a DLC release in the middle of the season
意味着在此期间会有新的DLC扩展内容被释出
so to balance
因此要使这些改动变得公平且均衡
this each team will play each other team once in the beginning of the season
在赛季之初每支队伍将会与其它所有队伍进行一场比赛
and then once again in the second half of the season
然后在赛季后半程进行第二场比赛
in the middle we'll have the major
在年中我们也会举办特锦赛
so there will always be high quality eSports content for you to enjoy
因此无论何时，你们所有人都可以享受到高质量的电竞比赛
let's passport to the end of this season
让我们来到赛季末期
the top tube teams from each region will continue to play in the land finals
每个赛区排名靠前的队伍将会继续进行线下决赛
however at the bottom of the bracket there have been some changes
然而在循环赛中排名垫底的队伍 他们的处境将会有所变化
now the bottom place Pro League team will be relegated to the Challenger League
今后处于联赛垫底的队伍将会被降级至Challenger League
replaced by the first-place challenger league team
而他的位置将会被Challenger League中排名第一的队伍取代
the team who finishes seventh place
而在Pro League排名第七位的队伍
in the pro league
则要与Challenger League中
will continue to play a relegation match against the second place challenger league team
排名第二的队伍继续进行降级赛
we hope that this change will incentivize up-and-coming Rainbow six teams
我们希望这样的改动可以激励越来越多的彩虹六号战队
as well as increase the overall skill level of our matches now
并且将我们从现在的比赛提升到越来越高的水准
let's take a look at how the format of the matches will change
让我们看一看下赛季的赛程改变
starting with the next season
将会带来怎样意想不到的惊喜
the first thing ,nothing new
第一件事，虽然并非新消息
（Philippe-Oliver Crépin/Esports Manager
菲利普-奥利佛·克雷平/电竞经理）
the first thing ,nothing new
第一件事情並不是新消息
（Philippe-Oliver Crépin/Esports Manager
菲利普-奥利佛·克雷平/电竞经理）
we announce it at the six Invitational
我们在彩虹六号国际邀请赛宣布
the pick and ban will be the official format of our six eSports
干员BP系统将作为正式赛制出现
at the beginning of each map
在所有比赛的每一大局的开局阶段
both teams will ban one attacker and one defender
两支队伍都会各自Ban掉一个进攻方干员和一个防守方干员
this new format will challenge the team's adaptation skills
这个新赛制将会挑战各个队伍的适应能力
and bring the mind games to a whole new level
并且会将心理博弈带到一个全新的高度
moving forward
接下来
let's take a look on how the rounds will be played through how a map
我们将通过每一大局的新赛制来看一看每一回合的新赛制有何变化
for the pro league regular season
在职业联赛的常规赛季
the matches will be played on the best of one
每场比赛将采用BO1赛制
the teams will stick to the same side for the first five consecutive rounds
每一大局的前五回合，各个队伍将不进行攻防互换
after that we have half time
在这之后，我们会有中场休息
which means a switch will occur from attack to defense
也就是说在这时会进行攻防互换
the first team that win six rounds will win the map
率先拿下六回合的队伍将赢得这一大局的胜利
a total of ten rounds can be played out
有可能双方会打满十回合
and if the score of 5/5 occurs we have a tie
如果出现了5/5的平局
but don't worry the action is not stopping
别担心，比赛不会中止
when we move into the pro league finals
职业联赛赛季决赛时
we introduce the tie break
我们会加入加时赛
the tie break will be played on classic siege
加时赛将会采用经典的攻防互换赛制
with team switching from attack to defense each rounds
he first team that wins three rounds will be the champion of the match
率先拿到三回合胜利的队伍将成为整场比赛的冠军
that about sums up all the changes that we're covering today
这些就是今天我们为您带来的所有改动
we hope you guys are as excited as we are about the upcoming pro league seasons
希望各位和我们一样都对即将到来的职业联赛赛季十分兴奋
and for more information on rainbow 6
要获取关于彩虹六号的更多信息
be sure to check out our website at rainbow6.com
请前往我们的官网Rainbow6.com